Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Records MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Video Productions, 1980-2014; 131.4 Linear Feet in 110 record cartons, 11 cassette boxes, 10 upright video containers, and 2 LP boxes.; 1000 U-matic; 339 MiniDV; 199 VHS; 108 Hi8; 46 Betacam_SP; 16 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 7 S-VHS; 4 Digital_Betacam; 2 DVCAM; 1 Betacam; 1 audiocassette; 2.06
  - Subseries VII.B: Non-Broadcast Videos, 1980-2014
    - The War: a community perspective, Feburary 12, 1991 (Box 119, U-matic 276_0819)
    - Harlem Black Activist, February 15, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_0768)
    - Day of Remembrance, Japanese Community Center, February 16, 1991 (Box 117, U-matic 276_0807)
    - Renu Nahata, February 18, 1991
      - Original master, undated (Box 181, Hi8 276_1064)
      - Hi8 recording, February 18, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_0762)
      - U-matic recording, February 18, 1991 (Box 126, U-matic 276_1078)
    - Simona Sharoni interviews Ilona and Simone, February 18, 1991
      - Tape one (Box 117, U-matic 276_0800)
      - Tape two (Box 117, U-matic 276_0798)
    - Jinsoo Kim interview CCR, Simone and Jessica -- Dub master, February 19, 1991 (Box 126, U-matic 276_1077)
    - Anti-Hussein T-shirts / WWII Graphics / Pastors for Peace, February 21, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_0764)
    - BMCC Conference -- Clark statement, February 21, 1991 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0760)
    - Interview with Joe Stork, February 21, 1991 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0755)
    - Seymour Melman, February 21, 1991
      - Cathy Scott and Dawn Suggs, Economic Conversion NY City, February 21, 1991 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1070)
      - Tape two, undated (Box 135, U-matic 276_1157)
      - Tape three, undated (Box 135, U-matic 276_1162)
    - Demo, Mash CO, February 21-23, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_1053)
    - "People vs. The Media" Panel, Keene State College, February 22, 1991 (Box 165, Vhs 276_1804)
    - Abyssinian Church Teach-in, February 23, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_0766)
    - Audubon demonstration, Harlem, February 23, 1991 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1059)
    - George Bush Conference, Nicaraguan Co. Street Theater, February 23, 1991
      - Original, cam A (Box 180, Hi8 276_0824)
      - Original, cam B (Box 180, Hi8 276_0825)
    - Michael Marsh #2, February 23, 1991 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1060)
    - Madre News Conference -- Nika Renfrew interview, February 27, 1991 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1057)
    - Jen -- Cultural Space, March 4, 1991 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0759)
    - Military Resistors Interviews, San Diego, Peter Bogdanovic, March 4, 1991 (Box 111, U-matic 276_0636)
    - Said, Columbia U., March 7, 1991 (Box 113, U-matic 276_0689)
    - Audio interview with Mutulu Shakur, March 8, 1991 (Box 126, U-matic 276_1076)
      Audio only
    - Wall of Women Against the War, San Francisco, March 8, 1991 (Box 133, U-matic 276_1130)
    - International Women's Day March, March 9, 1991
      - Tape one (Box 105, U-matic 276_0551)
      - Tape two (Box 105, U-matic 276_0552)
      - Ossie -- Master (Box 179, Hi8 276_0754)
      - May Ying -- Master (Box 179, Hi8 276_0753)
    - Union Women Speak Out -- Middle East Workshop, March 9, 1991
      - Hi8 recording (Box 179, Hi8 276_0756)
      - U-matic recording (Box 130, U-matic 276_0885)
    - Black Women's Speak Out, March 10, 1991
      - Part one, undated (Box 165, U-matic 276_1798)
      - Part two, undated (Box 165, U-matic 276_1799)
      - Tape two -- Donna Golden, Nzingha Clarke, March 10, 1991 (Box 180, Hi8 276_1041)
      - Tape two -- Donna Golden, Nzingha Clarke, March 10, 1991 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1061)
    - Mission from Cuba, United Nations, shot by Che Che, March 14, 1991 (Box 131, U-matic 276_0890)
    - Cathy Robbins Interview -- Dub, March 20, 1991 (Box 104, U-matic 276_0550)
    - May Ying Chen, March 21, 1991
      - Hi8 recording (Box 179, Hi8 276_0757)
      - Hi8 recording (Box 181, Hi8 276_1058)
    - Camp Lejeune, March 23-30, 1991
      - #1 -- Jen Lion, March 23-30, 1991 (Box 129, U-matic 276_1114)
      - #2 -- Jen Lion, March 23-30, 1991 (Box 129, U-matic 276_1115)
      - #3 -- Jen Lion, March 23-30, 1991 (Box 129, U-matic 276_1116)
      - Resisters reel, Jen Lion, undated (Box 129, Vhs 276_0875)
    - Global Dissent -- Source material, March, 1991
      - Claude Ake, Nigeria, March, 1991 (Box 117, U-matic 276_0802)
      - Interview with Gustavo Acosta, March 1, 1991 (Box 117, U-matic 276_0803)
    - Studio shoot #2, CTV -- SI, May 12, 1991 (Box 128, U-matic 276_1104)
    - Middle East Teach-in at John Jay College, Tape three, November 19, 1991 (Box 127, U-matic 276_1093)
    - Dongguan Fire, 1991 (Box 84, Vhs 276_0501)
    - Infinity Video Collective -- Interview with Eqbal Ahmad, 1991 (Box 117, U-matic 276_0801)
    - Ramsey Clark Press Conference, 1991, undated
      - Hi8 recording, February 11, 1991 (Box 181, Hi8 276_1068)
      - U-matic recording, undated (Box 109, U-matic 276_0617)
      - U-matic recording, undated (Box 109, U-matic 276_0616)
    - S.O.S. Haiti -- Source material, 1991-1998
      - Ben Dupuy Interview -- Tape one, undated (Box 149, U-matic 276_1612)
      - Ben Dupuy Interview -- Tape two, undated (Box 150, U-matic 276_1615)
      - Bertie Daniel Go to Washington, April, 1998 (Box 145, U-matic 276_0945)
      - Jerry Philogene Speaks with Edwidge Danticat -- Dub master, undated (Box 157, U-matic 276_1706)
      - Keith's footage, 1991 (Box 145, U-matic 276_0946)
      - Progres Interview / Titles, undated (Box 149, U-matic 276_1603)
    - L.A. Rebellion Street Interviews, NYC, May 1, 1992
      - American Liberty segment, 6 minutes (Box 75, U-matic 276_0327)
      - U-matic recording (Box 75, U-matic 276_0325)
      - VHS recording (Box 82, Vhs 276_0426)
    - Malcolm X Birthday Demonstration, May 19, 1992
      - Tape 1 -- Master (Box 75, U-matic 276_0329)
        Shot by May Ying Welsh
      - Tape 2 -- Master (Box 75, U-matic 276_0330)
      - Simone Farkondeh, Demonstration at United Nations, December 12 Movement (Box 75, U-matic 276_0328)
    - Interviews with Asians on Koreatown (CAAV), May 21, 1992 (Box 75, U-matic 276_0322)
    - March on the U.N. for Malcolm X's Birthday -- Dub master, May, 1992 (Box 138, U-matic 276_1349)
    - A Good Kill -- Dailies, day 6, for Greg Tilson, September 28, 1992 (Box 83, Vhs 276_0477)
    - Native American Teach-In, October 3, 1992
      - Tape 1 (Box 178, U-matic 276_1915)
      - Tape 2 (Box 178, U-matic 276_1916)
      - Tape 3 (Box 178, U-matic 276_1917)
      - Tape 4 (Box 178, U-matic 276_1918)
    - Edit Master, November 21, 1992 (Box 151, Betacam sp 276_1644)
    - Tactical TV -- Next Five Minutes, Holiday Grab Bag -- Master, December 22, 1992 (Box 151, U-matic 276_1638)
    - News footage on L.A. riots, circa 1992
      - Tape 1 (Box 75, U-matic 276_0331)
      - Tape 2 (Box 75, U-matic 276_0323)
      - Miscellaneous news shots (Box 75, U-matic 276_0326)
      - U-matic recording (Box 75, U-matic 276_0324)
    - Austria Window Master with German subtitles, 1993 (Box 149, U-matic 276_1611)
    - NAFTA: A 3 Way Tie for Last -- Source material, 1993, undated
      - #2, Tape #18 -- Niagara, J. Strauss, undated (Box 128, U-matic 276_1105)
      - #4 -- Che Che footage, SW Network, San Diego / Tijuana, undated (Box 128, U-matic 276_1109)
      - #9 -- May Day protest speeches part 2 with TC Window, May 1, 1993 (Box 128, U-matic 276_1112)
      - Campaign for Peace and Democracy, Part one, undated (Box 128, U-matic 276_1106)
        PAL encoding system
      - Campaign for Peace and Democracy, Part two, undated (Box 128, U-matic 276_1108)
      - C-Span -- Linda Fuendes (Canadian woman), undated (Box 128, U-matic 276_1107)
      - May Day / Jose La Luz, Elaine Bernard, undated (Box 129, U-matic 276_1113)
    - Breaking the Communications Blockade -- Pastors for Peace -- Master, March 24, 1994 (Box 149, U-matic 276_1607)
    - Mix [title in Arabic], 1994 (Box 178, Vhs 276_1920)
    - Contract on America Shoot -- Tetsuo's Shots, April 8, 1995 (Box 151, U-matic 276_1645)
    - WRL -- Prisons for Profit #2, April 21, 1995 (Box 188, Hi8 276_1562)
    - Cooper Union Teach-In -- Mumia Abu-Jamal, Tape two, May 21, 1995 (Box 156, U-matic 276_1694)
    - Telecom Interview #2 -- Master, May 4, 1996 (Box 186, Hi8 276_1451)
    - Signal to Noise -- Production elements, 1996, undated
      - Elements, undated (Box 148, U-matic 276_0993)
      - Excerpt for PBS Series, 1996 (Box 149, U-matic 276_1605)
    - Freedom Ride Short -- Master, 1996 (Box 151, U-matic 276_1641)
    - Salloum, 1996, undated
      - L2 -- Master, undated (Box 122, U-matic 276_0860)
      - Telecommunication Show, George Stony Interview, Frank Beecham -- Master, June, 1996 (Box 108, U-matic 276_0590)
    - Clark Kissinger -- "OJ Simpson: White Shame" Backup, April 9, 1997 (Box 188, Hi8 276_1574)
    - Haitian Churches Mobilizing for Immigration Rally, June 22, 1997 (Box 144, U-matic 276_0936)
    - Haitian Immigration Rally, July 3, 1997
      - Tape one (Box 145, U-matic 276_0947)
      - Tape two (Box 144, U-matic 276_0937)
    - Disney Demonstration, August 13, 1997 (Box 145, U-matic 276_0942)
    - City Hall Demonstration Against Police Brutality, August 29, 1997 (Box 145, U-matic 276_0943)
    - Saude Mitos and Verdades -- Stress E Coracao, August 1997 (Box 84, Vhs 276_0514)
    - Newsstands Below Houston B-Roll, People on the Street, December, 1997 (Box 149, U-matic 276_1608)
    - Gallery TV, Brazil, 1997 (Box 83, Vhs 276_0463)
    - Show Openers, January, 1998 (Box 147, U-matic 276_0974)
    - March for Workers' Rights, May 2, 1998 (Box 184, Hi8 276_1384)
    - Indonesian Riot Footage, May 13, 1998 (Box 122, U-matic 276_0862)
      Dub from Beta
    - Zine Production B-Roll, August 29, 1998 (Box 188, Hi8 276_1575)
    - E. Danticat Reading at NKIRU Books -- B-Roll version, September 17, 1998 (Box 149, U-matic 276_1604)
    - Academia Interviews, 1998
      - Lawrence Soley -- Master, April 26, 1998 (Box 149, U-matic 276_1609)
        Dub from Hi8
      - Laurence Soley, undated (Box 150, Vhs 276_1626)
      - Nancy Kranck -- Master, November 7, 1998 (Box 149, U-matic 276_1610)
      - Nancy Kranick, undated (Box 150, Vhs 276_1625)
    - Dolls and Dust, Thailand / HK, 1998 (Box 83, Vhs 276_0459)
    - Taxi Demonstration, 1998
      - Demonstration footage, July 1, 1998 (Box 184, Hi8 276_1387)
      - Demonstration footage, July 1, 1998 (Box 184, Hi8 276_1388)
      - Streetscape, 1998 (Box 184, Hi8 276_1386)
      - Streetscape, Ads in Times Square, June 20, 1998 (Box 186, Hi8 276_1450)
    - Noam Chomsky Interview at MIT, February 19, 1999
      - Tape one (Box 144, Betacam sp 276_0931)
        Dub from DVCAM
      - Tape two (Box 144, Betacam sp 276_0932)
      - Camera A (Box 143, U-matic 276_0921)
      - Said's Interview on Palestine (Box 143, Vhs 276_0928)
      - Statement on Independent Media, B-Roll (Box 144, Betacam sp 276_0933)
    - Spygroove -- Final Avid cut, March 10, 1999 (Box 116, Vhs 276_0728)
    - IAC Serbia Stop Bombing, April 7, 1999
      - Tape one (Box 185, Minidv 276_1427)
      - Tape two (Box 185, Minidv 276_1430)
    - IAC Demo and Interview footage, April 1999 (Box 80, U-matic 276_0394)
    - Howard Zinn -- Classroom, May 14, 1999
      - Opening (Box 188, Hi8 276_1577)
      - Hi8 recording (Box 186, Hi8 276_1502)
    - Source G.C., May 25, 1999 (Box 167, U-matic 276_0417)
    - Queer Pride, Burn The Mayor, El Fuego de Rudey, June 28, 1999 (Box 179, Minidv 276_0635)
    - Sister Spit Meow Mix, July 24, 1999
      - Tape one (Box 184, Minidv 276_1307)
      - Tape two (Box 182, Minidv 276_1187)
    - Burn The Mayor, July 28, 1999 (Box 82, Hi8 276_0452)
    - Green Chimneys -- Source material for Homecoming Queens, July, 1999, undated
      - GC 1: Javier Interview outside G.C. Jonathan-Javier, Aldeman, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0646)
      - GC 1: Javier interview outside Green Chimneys, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0701)
      - GC 2: Interview tape, Aldeman, Meischa, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0631)
      - GC 2: Meischa and Aldumen's interviews, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0702)
      - GC 3: Cluedy interview, Aldumen speaks, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0705)
      - GC 3: Cluedy interview, Mentor program, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0647)
      - GC 4: Goodbye Javier, Cake, July 21, 1999 (Box 115, U-matic 276_0708)
      - GC 4: Green Chimney, Cake, July 21, 1999 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0652)
      - GC 5: Reading Camera Instruction, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0641)
      - GC 5: Reading Camera Instructions, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0703)
      - GC 6: Javier tape / Drag Party, July 23, 1999 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0634)
      - GC 6: Javier tape 1, July 23, 1999 (Box 111, U-matic 276_0660)
      - GC 6: Javier tape 2, July 23, 1999 (Box 111, U-matic 276_0659)
      - GC 7: Deconstruct Commercial, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0632)
      - GC 7: Deconstructing media with Jerry Aldumen and Javier, undated (Box 115, U-matic 276_0707)
      - GC 8: Green Chimneys #1, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0642)
      - GC 8: Green Chimneys #1 First Day, undated (Box 111, U-matic 276_0662)
      - GC 9: Snake Tape, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0649)
      - GC 9: Snake Tape/Door, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0700)
      - GC 10: Aldumen dancing, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0650)
      - GC 10: Jawbreaker, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0648)
      - GC 10: Jawbreaker + Aldumen dancing, undated (Box 111, U-matic 276_0661)
      - GC 11: President in Park and Drag, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0651)
      - GC 11: President in Park and drag, undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0699)
      - GC 12: Misha's footage, sexercises, interviews (part 2), July 14, 1999 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0644)
      - GC 12: Shooting the interviews (classroom), undated (Box 115, U-matic 276_0710)
      - GC 12: Shooting the interviews (part 1), July 13, 1999 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0639)
      - GC 13: Green Chimneys #4, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0653)
      - GC 13: Green Chimneys meeting in Becky's Office (aka #4), undated (Box 114, U-matic 276_0698)
      - GC 13: Javier/Aldeman, undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0645)
      - GC 14: Cluedy interview #2 (USA), undated (Box 179, Hi8 276_0640)
      - Green Chimney's tampon commercial, undated (Box 115, U-matic 276_0706)
      - Green Chimneys -- Interviews, July 8, 1999 (Box 179, Hi8 276_0643)
      - Green Chimneys -- STD Drama, undated (Box 148, Vhs 276_0986)
      - Green Chimneys Tour, August, 1999 (Box 115, U-matic 276_0709)
      - Green Chimneys -- Selects, undated (Box 111, Vhs 276_0655)
    - AIDS Drugs for Africa Demonstration -- Master, August 23, 1999 (Box 185, Hi8 276_1391)
    - Cleudy (Lisa) interview #2, September 20, 1999 (Box 114, U-matic 276_0704)
    - WTO Interviews -- Tape one, October 28, 1999 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1536)
    - Demonstration at U.S. Department of Commerce -- Stop Drug Profiteering, November 30, 1999 (Box 184, Hi8 276_1385)
    - World AIDS Day: Out of the Darkness, Judson Memorial Church, December 1, 1999
      - Tape one (Box 184, Minidv 276_1301)
      - Tape two (Box 183, Minidv 276_1290)
    - WTO Opening Segment, December 29, 1999 (Box 136, Betacam sp 276_1330)
    - Million Youth March II, 1999
      - Tape one (Box 145, U-matic 276_0948)
      - Tape two (Box 144, U-matic 276_0935)
    - Esperanza Gardens -- Source material for Play for Keeps, 1999-2000, undated
      - Appellate Court Protest, undated (Box 146, U-matic 276_0959)
      - Newscasts of Bulldozing Crosswalks, Interviews, Video Stills, undated (Box 146, U-matic 276_0958)
      - Summertime, June - July, 1999 (Box 146, U-matic 276_0953)
      - Earth Celebrations, Bulldozer, Tour, undated (Box 146, U-matic 276_0954)
      - 7th Street Tour, February 21, 2000 (Box 146, U-matic 276_0960)
      - Selects From Tapes 1-6, undated (Box 146, U-matic 276_0955)
      - Community Gardens -- La Plaza, Esperanza, undated (Box 146, U-matic 276_0956)
    - Martin Luther King House Takeover / March, January 15, 2000 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1212)
    - Bus Riders' Union -- Camera master, August 15, 2000 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1422)
    - Vox Populi: "Independent Media Centers on the Rise," Hunter College, November 2, 2000 (Box 140, U-matic 276_1372)
      Dub from Betacam SP
    - "Freedom, Sovereignty, and Other Endangered Species" with Noam Chomsky Day 1, November 13-16, 2000
      - Day one, November 13, 2000 (Box 186, Minidv 276_1498)
      - Day two, Part one, November 14, 2000 (Box 186, Minidv 276_1496)
      - Day two, Part two, November 14, 2000 (Box 186, Minidv 276_1497)
      - Day three, November 16, 2000 (Box 186, Minidv 276_1499)
      - Day three, November 16, 2000 (Box 186, Minidv 276_1500)
    - Palestine Demonstration, November 19, 2000 (Box 141, Vhs 276_1379)
    - Art Action Demonstration, November 20, 2000 (Box 141, Vhs 276_1377)
    - Naher El Bared, February 12, 2001
      - MiniDV recording (Box 187, Minidv 276_1546)
      - MiniDV recording (Box 187, Minidv 276_1548)
    - Bush vs. Gore: Election vs. Selection? / Protest Demonstrations, Long Island, NY, September 6-9, 2001 (Box 116, Vhs 276_0785)
    - Fatimé Dam -- 9/11 on TV, September 11, 2001 (Box 178, Vhs 276_1921)
    - World Trade Center footage and news coverage, September, 2001
      - Footage and interviews, September 11, 2001 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1221)
      - News coverage -- Bush to Congress, undated (Box 150, Vhs 276_1622)
      - News coverage -- Carlos Pareja #1, September 13, 2001 (Box 178, Vhs 276_1927)
      - News coverage -- Carlos Pareja #3, September 13, 2001 (Box 151, Vhs 276_1635)
    - Marie Pierre Interview, Follow Up Show, November 15, 2001 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1411)
    - Hunter Rally for Immigrant Students, November 28, 2001 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1410)
    - I've Been Framed Mix, Guest Curators -- Master, November, 2001 (Box 142, Betacam 276_1592)
    - 9/11 Project -- Wall Street Interview, December 6, 2001 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1413)
    - Lebanon Dream, 2001 (Box 116, Vhs 276_0789)
    - Roots Workshop, 2001, undated
      - Part one -- Coco Recruit, undated (Box 187, Minidv 276_1525)
      - Part two -- Greg Payton Interview, April 3, 2001 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1524)
      - Part four -- Urbanmindz, Recruit Station, undated (Box 187, Minidv 276_1523)
      - Part five -- Street Protest, Interviews, undated (Box 187, Minidv 276_1522)
    - Students for Justice in Palestine, UC Berkeley Demonstrations, 2001-2002
      - MiniDV recording, 2001-2002 (Box 188, Minidv 276_1935)
      - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 185, Minidv 276_1433)
    - 9/11 "Who's Paying the Price" Rally, City Hall, January 2, 2002
      - MiniDV recording (Box 185, Minidv 276_1408)
      - VHS recording (Box 150, Vhs 276_1629)
    - 9/11 "Who's Paying the Price" Workers Rally, January 16, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1402)
    - Marriott Meetings with Workers, January - February, 2002
      - Workers at CIF, January 21, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1404)
      - MiniDV recording, January 23, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1403)
      - Mannela #1, February 27, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1406)
      - Mannela #2 and P.R. Response, February 27, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1405)
    - Pagan, February 1, 2002 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1005)
    - City Project, Glen Pasanen, April 5, 2002
      - Tape one (Box 185, Minidv 276_1414)
      - Tape two (Box 185, Minidv 276_1415)
    - Jobs Not Tax Breaks Rally, April 15, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1407)
    - Bertha Lewis, ACORN, June 8, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1412)
    - Wall Street, Chinatown, Lower East Side Footage, July 2, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1423)
    - NYC Skyline Pans at Dusk, August 1, 2002 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1409)
    - Columbia Conference Tape 3 -- South Africa Discussions, September 21, 2002 (Box 184, Minidv 276_1324)
    - NION, October 5, 2002 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1532)
    - Street Interviews, Brooklyn, October 7, 2002 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1544)
    - Texas State Education Board, Austin, 2002
      - Tape two, Part two, March 23, 2002 (Box 148, Vhs 276_0990)
      - Tape one, Part two / Tape two, Part one, August 23, 2002 (Box 150, Vhs 276_1620)
    - United Nations Demonstration News, January 27, 2003 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1417)
    - Bush State of Union Plus Post-Game Lies, January 28, 2003 (Box 178, Vhs 276_1922)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Palestine Video, February 9, 2003 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1435)
    - PAL March Audio, February 15, 2003 (Box 186, Minidv 276_1444)
    - Anti-War Demonstration -- Rachel Corrie, March 22, 2003 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1437)
    - Anti-War Colombian Activists, March 26, 2003 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1401)
    - "End the Occupation" March, October 25, 2003 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1399)
    - My Terrorist, 2003 (Box 116, Vhs 276_0782)
    - People of Color March, 59th Street -- Master, 2003 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1431)
    - TV Plus! #7, 2003 (Box 83, Vhs 276_0466)
    - Women's March, DC, April 25, 2004
      - Rally speakers (Box 185, Minidv 276_1393)
      - March footage (Box 186, Minidv 276_1519)
    - Draft Town Hall Tape #1, August 11, 2004 (Box 184, Minidv 276_1319)
    - New York Times and Foreign Policy, November 14-16, 2004
      - Part two, November 14, 2004 (Box 186, Minidv 276_1445)
      - MiniDV recording, November 16, 2004 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1547)
    - Intimate Reading and Chroma-key / War Culture / Broadcasts from Home, 2004 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1207)
    - Make the Roads by Walk Interview Reel, July, 2005 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1943)
    - Street Interview -- Hilary, March 20, 2006 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1429)
    - Military Myths, IVAW, Alternatives, July 25, 2006 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1527)
    - "Stop the War" Direct Action, March 19, 2007 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1420)
    - Going Postal B-Roll, NYC Post Offices, 2007, undated
      - MiniDV recording, June 5, 2007 (Box 185, Minidv 276_1395)
      - MiniDV recording, undated (Box 185, Minidv 276_1418)
    - Workshop, Interviews, B-roll, USSF, 2007 (Box 182, Minidv 276_1192)
    - Drop the Rock, March 27, 2008
      - Part one, undated (Box 189, Minidv 276_1020)
      - Part two, March 27, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1026)
      - Part three, March 27, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1008)
      - Part four, undated (Box 189, Minidv 276_1021)
    - Slave Theater -- Tape one, April 9, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1010)
    - Community Gardeners Forum, CUNY, May 31, 2008
      - Tape one (Box 189, Minidv 276_0999)
      - Tape two (Box 189, Minidv 276_1017)
      - Tape three (Box 189, Minidv 276_1029)
    - Rug, Tape one, June 8, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1011)
    - East Harlem Community Gardens, Tape one, July 7, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1028)
    - Brook Park Interview #2, July 8, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_0997)
    - Nick Powers, Sean Bell Interview, July 10, 2008
      - Part one (Box 189, Minidv 276_1023)
      - Part two (Box 189, Minidv 276_1024)
    - Gardens Project -- Brook Park, Harry Bubbins, July 16, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1025)
    - Carl Dix Interview on Sean Bell, July 17, 2008 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1003)
    - Veterans Day Parade Interviews, November 11, 2008
      - MiniDV recording (Box 182, Minidv 276_1229)
      - MiniDV recording (Box 189, Minidv 276_1009)
    - Election Show Interviews #1, 2008 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1531)
    - Rent-A-Center Interview and Press Conference, January 8, 2009
      - Hammond Interview, undated (Box 189, Minidv 276_0998)
      - Press Conference, January 8, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1004)
    - New Life Tabernacle, January 26, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1002)
    - Worm Composting, February 15, 2009
      - Tape one (Box 189, Minidv 276_0970)
      - Tape two (Box 189, Minidv 276_0971)
    - Taharka, Church, Rent-A-Center, Women's Lunch, March 28, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1007)
    - Anti War Compilation -- Dub master, July 19, 2009 (Box 183, Minidv 276_1247)
    - Street Art Takeover Adrienne, October 25, 2009 (Box 184, Minidv 276_1322)
    - Street Art Media Coverage, December 2, 2009
      - MiniDV recording (Box 186, Minidv 276_1505)